all right we're
live welcome everyone it's February 7th
2025 and we are in active INF for ant
stream
11 looking forward to a lot of feedback
interactivity and pl text fun and
learning all the pushes during the
stream are going to be going to the repo
doxology SL
cognitive and let's get right into it
all right so previously on active INF
foran streams we've heavily featured the
cursor development environment tool and
that's going to continue to be used as
well as seen a little bit with code viz
and that's going to come into play again
and in this stream for plain text
surprise education and Delight we're
going to be working a lot with obsidian
so
obsidian at the repo or website obsidian
DMD is a plain text note linking
software open source and it is going to
facilitate us doing some truly awesome
things with plain Tex repos and playing
back and forth between cursor and
obsidian is going to go really far so
here in the obsidian window on the left
side we're looking at the same file that
on
GitHub can be found
here and in cursor can be found here so
we have two local versions of infan
stream10 DMD so if we delete something
like starting with a GitHub push save it
in cursor that's going to be gone in
obsidian obsidian uses a linking style
where two brackets
open up the ability to make a Linker so
that is going to be reflected visually
in this graph version so before we go
too deep in this is some incipient
exciting relevant development work it's
semi structured so don't let the graph
and the
weave make too much light of the fact
that if we zoom out of course there's
more to paint into than
not and looking forward to people's
collaboration and contributions you can
head over to the repo while the stream's
happening or afterwards or if you're
watching live definitely put some funny
questions and ideas into the live chat
and we'll bring them into the repo and
that will weave that
way big picture we're going to be in
some ways that were not really even
possible a few years ago in integrating
theoretical foundations writing them on
the Fly and connecting with practical
implementations so we can delete that
and then we can see okay now we just
updated a plain text file so let's just
make that push just for fun okay where
do you even begin so welcome an overview
of obsidian usage so this could have
been typed
in manually like this
two
brackets
obsidian usage when we click on that
link it's like Wikipedia we head over to
this
article and there's going to be links in
the article the ones that are brightened
are the ones where there is a page and
the ones that are dim there's no page
yet and so if we click on that it makes
that page at the top level of the repo
so we don't need that at this point
but let's look a little bit at obsidian
usage and this is a markdown format
everything is these plain text markdown
files okay so file names link directly
file name vertical line Alias uses
custom text if you want it to say
something different than the file name
and here we have some machine readable
information and then over on the graph
side we can filter down and try to see
what's in the neighborhood of obsidian
usage there's going to be a lot of
active inference generative models in
this stream as well but first I just
wanted to start this way so here we are
and when we have our cursor there we get
this colorful highlight of obsidian
usage and everything that it's linked to
in the plain text gets rendered as an
edge here so we can drag around that
play with that we can okay hm okay
obsidian usage plain text benefits let's
check out plain text benefits wow
Version Control Knowledge Management
machine readability research
benefits all these different benefits
which cursor wrote entirely for me and
we'll get to how and where that happened
okay back to the top level and let's
carry on with a stream so previous
streams we've been using different
synthetic intelligence and live chat
methodologies for having a great time
learning about what other than active
inference and the free energy principle
so let's check out those articles again
these were written entirely using cursor
so what that looked like was let's head
over to knowledge
base
mathematics we can go over to some
active inference article so here's the
plain text article this is it
in
obsidian so here we have everything from
software examples to it could be
anything if we want to use AI to update
this active inference
article bring it in with control I to
the composer mode and then we can say
add
fantastic
comprehensive relevant length
and structured typo new sections to the
active
article so now if we head over to active
inference we see it's connected to a
whole variety of different terms and
topics and
ideas so very cool how also by embedding
a docs set
ction there's a lot of obsidian style
also just picking up from Context this
is so here is Claude uh 3.5 Sonet 2024
1022 I've added four major new sections
to the active inference article so here
in the green are these new sections that
just got added again you'll remember
from earlier infer an streams where
anything above like 200 lines of code
was getting cut off now we're into the
1400 lines of code so that was pretty
simple edit we'll accept it but it
changes the graph and you can watch
cursor modifying files and then it's
popping up and the graph topology is
evolving so here's free energy principle
and these gray nodes are all
hypothetical links so they're linked
kind of um in a preemptive way we can
turn on to just existing files if we
want to look at the more dense
weaving of okay well how about
variational calculus this comes up like
all the time all right here we have
different
math different examples different
applications of variational inference
and these on a line by line basis can be
vetted in different ways and researched
by different individuals so if we were
like tags I I'll add a tag whatever it
is and then that can be versioned and if
people disagree they can use the other
version of the plain text
file hey Andrew yeah there's going to be
some really fun applications here okay
so let's now go
to the
agenda so free energy principal article
just briefly also super long article
with all of this machine readable
information we're going to explore
explore a bunch of fun plain text oh and
that change so here's where we are
here's stream 10 Connected To ACM and
F and then when we delete this
line it
disconnects um briefly going to go
through the dock part of the repo to
show a little bit of the meta structure
on the cognitive repo and then we're
going to get into pdps partially
observable Markov decision processes our
favorite kind of dropa model creature
for active inference and ants and
bioherms and more oh brother so here we
go first into the
uh this config folder looks empty could
have been it's a simulation config we'll
leave it there for now maybe it's not
even important okay here's a
documentation road map here it is in
cursor here's documentation in obsidian
and a readme for the documentation some
of this might seem like Overkill however
ever as long as it's accurate and gives
linking valid structure this is
incredibly effective with cursor and
composer so first API that's not really
being used at this point but there's a
lot of discussion around agent apis and
so having these comprehensively linked
versions of files in plain text super
powerful but not really going to come
into play here Concepts this is just
documentation for Concepts so that are
relevant for the package but not
scientific Concepts per se more like
Concepts that are relevant for the
documentation at a meta level so that
when we say well we're really interested
in machine
readability that kind of semantics is
going to get across just fine but if we
provide a ton of
linking so that machine readability is a
full knowledge node then it can be even
more effective and it can have these
mermaid diagrams so then when we're
giving a talk and we're going well free
energy principle we want to have
reproducibility and research integrity
and that's why we're studying this
cognitive phenomena with machine
readability those are just paths Just
Around the Horn 643 double play
um examples these are some examples of
documentation again it's really not the
most exciting afternoon reading per se
but it gets really far with helping
cursor guides these are guides for
different micro standard operating
protocols for cursor and agents and
these can be taken out to extreme levels
of intensity so again it could be
followed by a person or it can just be
used with these absurd levels of
hierarchical
dispatch research here's an example of a
research plan that was written for the
ant colon simulation that we might look
at
later templates these are template for
different folders of the knowledge base
repo component that we'll go to in a
second and then tools so here's some
hints for cursor and the cursor files
information that help development in
this augmented Niche and it can be used
also to list other autonomous AI tooling
so it could be like search literature
database or drive numerical belief from
natural language any of these things
that people have been exploring for
years and also using obsidian so let's
just make that file longer obsidian
usage make this
obsidian use
file much comprehensively longer and
with some
relevant
linked files comma make them fully
so this is using the agent mode which
right now only exists for the Claude
family I believe however we may expect
and prefer not so long when many of
these models from the open AI family
from the Google from various other labs
are useful and integration with local
language models all these kinds of
things are more and more useful and
possible every day so I'm in the slow
usage tier in the slow lane right now
because of what has been happening over
the last several days we'll just let
that
cook maybe it'll make some changes while
we're look at it but let's carry on for
now okay that was just the documentation
folder structured approaches for
building documentation and advancing
documentation from any current state and
forensically reconstructing
documentation these are some truly
incredible opportunities okay now we get
into the knowledge base itself things is
where we're going to see the active
inference models but I want to walk
through these top sections CU they're
really fun okay let's go over to systems
theory so here's systems theory we can
see already that it's going to link to
cognitive phenomena it's going to link
to swarm intelligence it's going to link
to to an index file so here's a short
Linker article on systems theory and we
can follow some of these links like how
about information Theory and we can
follow this
all written iteratively through
cursor and every single line could be
checked there could be a person there
could be any number of other
approaches here's what the obsidian
update is doing so it's like okay and it
gets it that we're within an obsidian
repo so here now it's updating the
obsidian documentation for
itself there's probably some points of
diminishing return but it just wrote
several hundred lines and then now it's
going okay well let's make a new linked
file for network analysis so here it
created this whole new file for network
analysis very of course meta since this
is what's happening over here and that
that can be
done in
multiple
different
Maneuvers by
one press here so these are new articles
that it's
writing okay back to the knowledge base
here are the different areas citations
I've left empty citation format and
bringing in full text that's a whole
another topic not not for this repo this
time um there's agents which is
documentation on specific agents so here
it's a full article o and s space uh o o
I added just manually to as an example
of one that we can uh build right now s
space this is a whole article with
linkages on S Laten state or hidden
state so we can have mega connect with
the active inference ontology and this
helps
entrench different understandings so
that when it's like a
matrix here's exactly what the structure
is this it repeat giving multiple
explanations so it is wild times for
years it's like well what really is the
a matrix or what is the or how how are
different ways to write it or what
letter should we use or what's the most
interesting it's like we're kind of in a
position now where
it's more about the
underlying entrenchment of understanding
plus perhaps we could say the
crystallized or classically modified
understanding of each of these
variables and then the more fluid
situational and contextual deployment of
these structures so let's have the
oace article get written
so in agents generic
PDP
space here write the o space article
fully about the observation
space okay so now we're looking at this
graphical relational Matrix
describing the knowledge
Network describing a PDP
structure so here in the PDP structure
it's like hey when I say PDP these are
the components that I mean so oace was
empty it's still getting written but
we're going to see the graph structure
change let's see if we can catch it live
changing now oace has been written
lines so it relates to all these other
topics so there's like a two-way
mapping okay I guess observation it does
relate to this concept of observation
structure should we have an extensive
human Human Experience debating whether
or not observation structure should be
its own page or this page or that page
or the first slide in your presentation
or this or that it's like maybe not but
having it as a hypothetical node that we
can continue to unpack iteratively and
crawl through is it's another level and
type
of post Wikipedia knowledge
engineering but
maybe bringing back the relevance for
Wiki and and pl Tex collaborative design
tools as well so here we are in O now we
can see the structure of the PDP
flushing out so we were looking through
the generic PDP documentations like
levels of
documentation that I don't even know
have been seen for some of these topics
because we can always just go into a
given
Matrix vastly expand the comprehensive
article on B
Matrix these are the kinds of thrilling
articles that I'm sure many of the
listeners and viewers and live Chatters
love to write in in their uh spare time
but uh now we are getting assistance
with writing these fun
articles let's look at the B
Matrix and it's going to be evolving its
topology so that's the PDP we also of
continuous time agent that we'll get to
uh citations again there's none at this
point cognitive cognitive uh there's a
variety of cognitive mechanisms there or
cognitive phenomena this is very similar
to the work we did in the atlas project
at cogc related to pattern languages for
cognitive phenomena so here in the
cognitive phenomena so here's the
improved extended article on the B
Matrix
so there's
more connections to computational topics
more connections to how we like to see
it
implemented more math foundations and
then someone can spin it however they
want like you know the classic right the
who's on
first to understand the B Matrix from a
perspective where I don't know much math
past middle
school so custom generative
multilanguage multimodal educational
materials is in the game updates push it
to
GitHub so it it interpreted that perhaps
because of the previous context with
writing a new knowledge format so it's
going to write a new document called B
Matrix Basics so we'll see what it comes
up with there um cognitive
phenomena let's see it in cursor
cognitive phenomena here we'll use
control K so we can do inline coding
we'll say fastly
add phenomena to this
list here's B Matrix basics
here's the B Matrix
Basics
fun
relatable blogs of any format
to work through and ask
about back in the cognitive phenomena
world still in slow request Lane but we
have
500 lines of cognitive phenomena some of
them we already have nodes Pages for
others we don't but you could imagine
iteratively
applying prompts where there is a page
with no information Please write that
comprehensively vastly excellently
professionally Etc so that'll update
cognitive phenomena um but back to the
cognitive phenomena
folder we have all
these kind of like here's a empty
one but all of these on
demand
articles so almost surely trained on a
variety of articles about ants and
Collective behavior for
example but at the same time this is
coming up with machine readable schema
and
ontologies that you could have all the
mycologists in the world in a
room
and what they know of might come up with
a very high
correlation of these terms
and then it's always possible to just
add more terms if someone says wow it's
like well they they really came up with
a new term that should go here and then
that's where you can just add the new
term
directly and then build on the page and
then you have the page template and then
it links to the documentation and so on
so cognitive phenomena just a bunch of
times I uh iteratively applied a few
prompts just to get it to to make these
kind of Wiki style
articles on all these different topics
whether more as a Linker which is good
for making like a beach head into a new
epistemic frontier or a more advanced
article that has uh visualizations I
think for the cognitive phenomena one I
was just interested to get it to link as
much as possible which is why it has
this list format but then you say for
every single bullet point
expand that section so that it has three
sentences and then next prompt every
sentence split it to reify the main
point with an
example that's the cognitive section
okay mathematics so here it's pretty fun
because the the latc rendering is so
nice we can look at belief updating math
code
connections how about compute expected
free energy well here's the definition
of expected free energy in terms of
epistemic value and pragmatic value so
we have this more Wiki documentation
page but then when in the active
inference page it says it's going to use
use expected free
energy and then that is linked strongly
to the expected free energy page and
here's what we expect from expected free
energy so then when I prompt somewhere
else something like make an active
inference model or make an active
inference PDP model of this or that
situation
these highways and
highways are right there to trace it
back to where we have a human
interpretable versionable document so
again the era of like what is the best
way to convey expected free energy it's
like after what's happened in the last
48 hours in my experience I would
say in plain text accurately coherently
professionally Etc
and then with this generative layer
around
it that is able to recognize the
query and then connect it to what's
relevant to
generate but if we just dip our Ladle
into a given llm and say what is
expected free energy it it might give us
a totally valid response it might give
us a semi- memorized response from a
paper it might come to a emergent
synthetic definition from several papers
finding a semantic
interpolation that might be a better
version so it's it's not that anything
else that's not what I'm showing here is
ineffective it's that if someone's like
I like this notation system or this
should be included we can just very
modularly put that right into the plain
text so then if we want it explained and
say explain this for me as a
enthusiasts
of topic
X maybe it'll make a new file let just
see if it gives a funny shot Ju Just you
know what does it even think these
symbols mean I don't know all of us are
learning but again these are linked
topics and so I
was just studying and learning going
okay well okay so free
energy okay we can ask it could be
in
here add a section conveying at a big
technical Picture level what makes
something a free
energy who hasn't had that
question so we just keep adding
information
a b Matrix
Enthusiast whoa okay let's look at the B
Matrix Enthusiast
briefly that is in the generic PDP
guides as it basically should
be here's the basics here's the who's on
first style blog not
dialogue and then here's the B Matrix
enthusiast
if you've ever been fascinated by how
things change over time whether it's
weather patterns stock markets or even
your favorite video game characters
movement you're already thinking about
State transitions the B Matrix is a
powerful tool that helps us understand
and predict these changes why it's
cool and then it's like it is so cool
each of these topics really is so cool
and we
move around them through them in them on
them all that um we
could
write all the rest of the generic PDP en
Enthusiast files
comprehensively fully and
light-hearted it probably doesn't even
need the accurate information to be also
in the obsidian repo but it's like if
this is the stuff that we've already
looked at then it it definitely doesn't
hurt and then it's
on the cognitive repo anyone can just
download this
repo as well as make their own all of
this open source great times and then
supercharge their own llm use
so that if if we say um make a who's on
first dialogue about an elephant that is
using a b
Matrix to build a bridge but if we
already have elephant B Matrix build a
bridge who's on first as their own nodes
in a graph then it's just going to be so
much better and so much more
reproducible observation space it's
like how how could and
fun okay back to the repo then we'll get
through these guides and into the uh
simulation section so again these are
like on demand learning
articles that can't be necessarily taken
at
100% accuracy however the same could be
said for any document and these have the
ability to just
interactively make diagrams
links um so for example the path
integral work this is some recent work
in active inference and Fe that no one
is born do so how can we learn this well
there's going into a search engine and
trying to find documents based upon
backlinking or semantic similarity and
then reading the primary words that were
on that page
there's trying to find a textbook maybe
you have physical access maybe you have
digital access it's like or we can kind
of spin out a neighborhood like I did
several uh times next to the path
integral so connect path integral to the
FP and then okay well it's in plain text
here but I think if it
were clearly linked there just little
Nano edit I didn't even have to know
about the path integral didn't have to
write the paper but just that's a little
modular edit that changes the topology
of the
network that helps everyone learn and
apply all these topics so it's like or
what is an action principle these are
just things that can be asked in so
here's the oace
Enthusiast okay it wrote A S and O
here's what makes something a free
energy so interestingly this is common
erir it also deletes a bunch rest of
content remains unchanged so we'll
reject that
edit but some of these things are just
little little road bumps on the
speedrun here's the cognitive phenomena
we said add add phenomena to list
okay again here's a long edit that that
it it K the control K mode does that
sometimes so look for that but um these
ones we just added dozens of Articles
and then we can have an iterative prompt
or an iterative script that says go to
cognitive phenomena check to see if the
linked file is comprehensively written
make it better use an internet search or
use your local information thoughtfully
with whatever it happens to be and
you're just expanding your knowledge
base um which you can start from scratch
or you could pull what is in this repo
already um okay so that's the math
learning
component how is how is the tailor
series related to The Continuous time
agents operation in generalized
coordinates also something that many
have wondered these are specific
questions that it's it's like okay that
was a question about tailor series
expansion generalized coordinates
continuous time active inference
agents those
are on one hand big lifts initially but
on the other hand they fit so nicely
into our working memory and certainly
into the context window of these
synthetic intelligence artifacts so we
can ask those questions either directly
let's ask that exact question in a new
composer window see what happens how
does
a how
do how does a continuous time agents in
active
inference
use Taylor
series expansion
for navigation and intelligence
in generalized
coordinates that question could also
just be typed into or spoken to any
other llm interface
but here first off we could be working
totally offline and
locally with a local llm in these plain
text open source files or we can be
using what whatever it is that's
happening here so again just like what
are we uncertain about what are we
curious about what would be learning and
on the edge for us and then meta
cognition we state that
that's an action coming from us and then
write it don't just let that uncertainty
dissipate and then like okay I have this
reflex like it looks hard this looks
like it's going to be hard to read and
learn so at that point it's like is this
a lift that I'm ready to make at this
Nano moment am I ready to read about
this or is it like good enough to know
that there is an answer and maybe dump
it into a text file for later or maybe
um I'm I'm still struggling with this
can it be made into a who's on first
style dialogue Etc so that's the math uh
and that's the knowledgebase part so
this could contain summaries or semantic
embeddings or full texts for different
citations and different resources here I
just did totally abono from nothing of
all of these articles related to fun
topics okay moving on past the knowledge
base here we get into the SRC or source
file here is where we can start to
explore
reliable dis hyphen
intermediated calling of abstractions
for operational approaches to active
inference systems
engineering so this is a
dispatch it's kind of like calling
operator let's see it in
cursor okay here we're looking at the AC
inference dispatcher first let's just
look over in the graphical
view what's the neighborhood of the
active inference
dispatcher so these are just some
related
topics okay what the active inference
dispatcher does is it picks up at the
linguistic semantics of the active
inference ontology and then creates
Runners through
dispatch that send off to
implementational methods so if we say I
want to have an agent that uses
variational free energy on perception
for updated sense making and then you
could imagine whether we ask or state or
it asks us it's like okay let's do a
binary State space so it could be zeros
or ones coming in for
observations and then later we want to
add or change that to be in a continuous
State space like between zero and one
but also for those continuous values
we would still want to be able to use
the semantic
dispatch of variational free energy but
under the hood it's doing a different
kind of implementation because of it for
example being continuous versus discrete
so that's what this dispatch
intermediation is doing and similarly
like for the
biofirm this is a canvas this nice
feature of uh
obsidian take whole articles and lay
them out like this um as well as link
them to to non
articles similarly for the biofirm in
the
dispatch here is kind of like an
interface between the highlevel
semantics qualitative linguistic and
specific opinionations and routes for
lower level
implementations someone someone says I
want a red
adaptive funny
sedan someone doesn't need to say what
is the chemistry of the red paint such
that it has this wavelength of light
under it's just like well we could list
out multiple options or one option or
you could just hard code and say oh when
people say red they mean this exact kind
of iron oxide you you could you might
not be wrong in a give situation you
might not be wrong in a whole variety of
situations but it's not the most General
systems design approach so these SRC
files are like a repo of tools that we
want to use four different kinds of
methods that come into play like Matrix
operations so then there can be a matrix
operation like transpose Matrix and
let's just say that there's two methods
at our disposal and one of them works
well for small matrices and one if it's
a big one so then in the outside of the
SRC folder at the semantic level someone
can say transpose this Matrix at this
point in the program's logic and then
the dispatcher sends that to whichever
implementation is most relevant given
some other
criteria so that that's a little bit of
a stub folder there not a ton in there
but the the dispatch concept is going to
be critical and it's an example of
something that's enabled by the active
inference
ontology okay templates agent template
belief templates these allow a variety
of things again they're just examples of
templates but since the nodes in
obsidian being plain text files can also
be
anything templates can be wildly useful
because then they're used for so many
things okay now let's get into some of
the code sections for
tests all
right
so uh obsidian maybe there's some way to
configure it differently I just don't
have set up right now but it doesn't
display python files so here we can see
that in the tests folder and in the the
GitHub repo the all the files are there
but obsidian focuses on the markdown so
pros and cons to that but it's all good
um let's
uh open it and see what this
does okay this is a test
Suite okay made some
errors start a new compos window and
while it's fixing that let's look at the
outputs so these are some package level
tests just doing some Matrix
visualizations different kinds um of
simple visualizations and analyses so
not not super complex but the testing
framework is actually slightly more
complex than that so it can be used in a
variety of ways all right now we get
into the things this is exciting because
it it it also is pleasantly
surprising truly how rapidly and
absurdly some of these programming
capacities are advancing so I'm going to
start with possibly the most useful of
the things here which is the generic
PDP while it's fixing the tests over
there also in the uh settings
there's YOLO
mode where you can allow the commands to
be
run so here it's both able to propose
and then run and then get the terminal
feedback and then continue to iterate in
this closed loop so the compo the agent
mode is
like an order of magnitude or more
faster and now it finished all the tests
great here's what we did but that might
have taken me several key presses I know
I know several key PES to get to even
that and maybe I would have said
something in between that would have sty
it you know or maybe there is a place
where it gets itself into a cold Zach
and and I could have come into play but
suffice to say in this situation for
doing a uh hierarchical debug on the
testing infrastructure for a whole
package
I would not have been able to do that
with just one click even in
cursor a couple of weeks ago
probably okay let's go to the generic
PDP so this is an example of using
generalized notation notation GNN for
specification rendering implementation
execution uh analys visualization of
active inference generative models this
is
building in a very fun way on the work
with yakup from several years ago and a
lot of contributions that that uh in
questions people have had since for
making these obvious either manually
crafted or llm based transformations of
specifications into plain text formats
that we can then render different kinds
of models from
so here up top the the lower parts are
um some of them are are not used at this
stage in this version that I'm putting
out others are used to specify
visualization so this is kind of like a
whole um generative model level config
like learning parameters inference
parameters but the minimal config stuff
is up at the top which is the state
spaces so here we have and this this
gets back to our um o o space enjoyer um
B Matrix Enthusiast and so on we are
stating the number of discrete options
for observations oh space the number of
discret Laten spaces how many actions at
each time step the agent has how many
total time steps the simulation is going
to run for the planning Horizon for the
simulation which is how many time scales
is the agent going to combinatorically
do policy proposals
for um and some other features so where
this is going to go and then we'll run
it is here's the the plots so here's an
overview of our agents here's uh uh
5x4 a matrix up on the top
left here's just one action from the B
Matrix but we could look at the whole B
Matrix three actions these are the the B
matrices for each of those three AC so
pick like a
slice see just in this visualization
it's through time like time step uh 0 1
2 3 4 because I did have preference
learning fully operative and wanted to
prune it back to simplify it just a
little bit so now it can graph C
preferences through time constraints
cost but it's fixed Through Time D is
are prior on those four hidden States so
that's uh
flat and then e are prior on policy and
that's initially flat okay so these are
just the sub
components different outputs from
different belief updating through the
10 um the action distributions but the
the
visualization
that is new even to how I've seen what
it could output in the last several
weeks is here
we're we're looking
at three affordances per time
step and then we have the pragmatic and
epistemic
components which are the ep the the
expected free energy hashtag look at
that article playing out through each of
the time steps so here's a four planning
Horizon and this is like do you go low
medium or high and then here's low low
low low low here's low medium high low
so let's run it so in other words this
is the whole policy tree roll
out for a generic PDP
planner just from using generalized
notation notation in a well structured
Niche with some of these open source
components not even using pmdp or any
other kind of uh technique so let's make
a new generic PDP let's do six
observations projecting on to three
latent states with two
actions for 15 time steps with a
planning Horizon of five
okay here first what it does is
it does a sequential test
Suite where it starts a testing session
using the testing
infrastructure then it goes through and
lo logs these sub fully realized models
like let's build the Matrix and test the
size let's build it test the size
visualize it and so this helps
iteratively building and coding as well
or let's just do one belief update and
then see if it went the direction we
thought it was going to
go so now it runs
through and now it's
running the full PDP
and then it's going to be
outputting so previously there was
um five four and three five observations
four latent States three affordances
which is why we saw that Tri forcation
in the policy roll out
visualizations
now
here here we see policy bifurcation
because there's two affordances per time
step so here we have low and high of low
low low high
low and so this is a way to see the
expected free energy and the components
of expected free energy for a whole
policy tree
rollout I don't know if that has been
done even of a few weeks
ago and as kind of expected the
ambiguity Rises
at least in how this is
visualized so that took 76 seconds for
running this testing
Suite that ran an
informative sequence of events that
began with just testing
whether the the Machinery was in
order then went on through building some
of the sub
componentry operating them for short
periods of time and then working its way
up to ultimately something that is
outrageously useful for the octave
infrance which
is holographic representations of policy
tree rollouts with defined epistemic and
pragmatic value components and their
balance so that's a generic PDP
and then to not
leave obsidian out in the cold here's
the read
me here the read me is written like
software style
but we
could improve
it like
that so then
we have a a clear
link going from well here's the readme
for how the pdb is applied in that
folder and then here's the bigger
concept a matrix it's like what about
the a matrix oh yeah it defines the
mapping between hidden States the s
space and observations the o space
what's the s space Oh yeah it looks like
that so it is just tracing around all of
these different
aspects of the total semantic space but
we have ju deposed here docs which are
the ultra implementational or meta
implementational examples and concepts
for this repo as
repo then there's the knowledge base
ranging from the statistical
mathematical foundations on through the
agent level
documentation and including both
technical definitions like what is a b
Matrix
technical as you want it to get and then
what is an educational curriculum for
every single possible of this for every
single possible of
that and
then through the SRC Dispatch
Center we can have these
implementations that can be used in a
super Standalone way or in a really
integrated way so let's just look at a
few of the other implementation
this is also a kind of generative model
that I've never built
before and it's in the continuous time
setting okay so this one we're in the
continuous time setting and let's get
the test started so running the test
Suite in the continuous time setting
let's see it looks like over
in
obsidian okay here's the continuous
generic model so just like that generic
PDP was for discrete time discrete State
spaces partially observable marov
decision processes generalizations
including planning and other cognitive
phenomena # cognitive
phenomena here is continuous time
continuous St space active inference
agents the agent learns and operates in
continuous domains using modern deep
learning techniques while adhering to
active inference principles so it's
going to have these techniques and again
because it was in a little code Corner
the read me reads more like a GitHub
read me read me than a obsidian but we
can quickly evolve that by saying also
write a mega obsidian Style densely
linked
comprehensive continuous time model here
connecting
to and I'll just drag in docs a whole
folder and knowledge
base so let's see what it writes there
um but meanwhile back in the test Lance
so initialization shift operation
sensory mapping just the perceptual
sense making Els of the continuous time
situation then one time step of tailor
series expansion one free energy
computation one belief consistency check
and then several more
sophisticated tests leading on through
ultimately to tailor expansions in
generalized State space so here the
model has I'll just pick some random
variables this might slow down the the
computation
fastly three latent uh two latent States
three
observations four orders for the
generalized
coordinates 0.01 time step for
integration let's rerun the
tests so that took 94 seconds to run the
test Suite with that
previous one so meanwhile over in
continuous time active
inference so here's the obsidian
style article that it wrote
on what we asked to write about so let's
check out the neighborhood of that
article here's our big knowledge
Network and see if we can find and
there's the Red
Dot so here's continuous time active
inference and here's how it's idian
linked to all these
topics continuous time active
inference free energy
principle
okay all right now we'll start the tests
but meanwhile let's look at the outputs
from the previous continuous time
testing
okay I'm not even sure what these May
yield
okay some pre-flight checks on sensory
mapping how accurate was just our input
versus output was there even the right
correlation direction for sensory
mapping shift oper I don't know what
these numbers mean in the Json format
but you can ask please improve the
tests of continuous time agents to yield
many more
visualizations
okay but while we're looking at the
previous versions of the code
okay phas space predictions now maybe
this was just when when there was only
one or two orders for the model we could
have just been
fitting free energy generalized
coordinates to a point which might be
Overkill maybe we could have just
identified the point but some of these
visualizations like being able to
identify the gradient following and the
solenoidal iso Contour
following in a continuous facee space
okay this GIF looks
like it opened for a second though it
was just showing well let's see okay
that took 104 seconds so we we slightly
there's this
GIF it was being Rewritten while we were
looking at it okay so maybe it was just
a weird uh corner of State space maybe
there's some Mis implementation of
something maybe it doesn't but you know
we're we're in the ball
harmonic
motion
okay Maneuvers in state and phase
spaces and Taylor series
expansions so this looks like it's doing
a two order expansion with a position
which is like the first moment of the
Taylor series and then the first
derivative the velocity
and again maybe these numbers are
hardcoded maybe the implementation is
not perfect maybe it's not General s so
on but the infrastructure is in place
for building these things okay now the
test Suite has been graciously added
with these several hundred
lines we don't even need to type it in
we could have said continue to to run
that by
yourself okay uh I'm going to just
briefly show the other
things uh the biofirm and the ant colony
and then open to whatever ideas and
questions people have in the chat for
which um obsidian neighborhood should we
build
out which things should we build for
coding like
here um okay first ant colony this
one was almost in one
shot I just said write or read me and
then fully totally actually Implement an
ant colony active inference multi-agent
simulation so the kind of thing that
that was
years of wheel spinning in 2017 18 19 20
is being semi-autonomously one-shotted
by just a hope and a
dream um let's just see what it output I
don't know if it has
run basically it spins out the schema
for a whole multi-agent simulation now
is this going to be compliant with
insert your own favorite multi-agent
framework no not necessarily however if
in the document mentation we had a a
documentation for that and it was linked
to
multi-agents as one of the ways to do it
or the way to do it then it would be
structured that way let's just see if
it's already
operative okay ant
colony we'll run setup just to see if it
needs
that okay maybe it needs commands let's
just see if simulation
works
okay it's running the tests for the
continuous
generic case over off to the side but
it's like and then already you can see
how what I'm doing and showing with only
one and a half autonomous agents at any
given time it's already like the Farmers
Market local organic low throughput
version because why not just have this
dispatching truly programmatically
without a graphical interface or why not
have it
um in any number of other pretty
adjacent ways using the computer
operator using just uh headless machine
using just uh GitHub agents so many ways
to do it okay so now it's it is
proceeding through the extended test
Suite with A continuous time setting but
let's just pivot over to the ant colony
to see if we can get some ant gifs on
screen ensure that running this really
does fully
implement the total ant colony
simulation yielding
sophisticated analysis and many
hilarious do
GI so we'll see where it gets on the ant
colony but meanwhile over in the biofirm
land
so
biofirm I in one sentence summarized our
work on the biofirm project and said
write a read me and then spin out to
according to how it could be make it
happen something like that so it's a
homeostatic control model biofirm using
active inference principles for Biore
region management this implementation
demonstrates how active inference can be
used for maintaining system stability
through partial
observations so the biofirm implements a
PDP building copiously off of of course
the simple and the generic things
already in the adjacent folder and all
the knowledge docks that we already
looked
at it's going to use an a pmdp to do
this Biore Regional
homeostasis the model aims to maintain
system in homeostatic range by one
making observation from a simplified
three-state observation space or we
could combine homeostatic Biore Regional
nested
stewardship with the generic pomdp so
then it could be a different
observations space but just to fix it
for this current time two inferring the
true underlying five State
environments so here and and meanwhile
an Colony autonomous operation
ongoing here there's three observations
we're getting like we're getting high
medium low from the thermometer and then
there's five latent States so it could
be off one end or off off the other end
and then there's also these sort of
threshold regions with on the lower and
the upper bound you know or you could
have five observations and three latent
States that's why we need these plain
text formats and that's why we've been
developing them for years because it
isn't enough to just say well let's put
at three again you may be more than
right in a given situation but the
bigger picture is doing meta parameter
sweeping across configuration spaces for
even what one agent's cognitive model is
structurally let alone
quantitatively so three the biofirm
selects then actions from a set of three
decrease maintain or increase to keep
the system in the desired
state so it continues to go
through here's some of the technical
elements let's read this read me in
see
you so similarly this one could be
enriched with visualizations and all of
that make it a little bit less like uh
code read me a little bit more obsidian
formatted
um and what it runs
let's look at some of the outputs from
the
biofirm okay Granger
causality transfer entropy on
network convergent cross mapping not
sure what this one would be causal
impact not sure if it's calculated
accurately or in any specific way but
this brings us back back to the dispatch
operator like causal impact doesn't just
have one
formalism that's why there was a great
work in a live stream with like the 18
def different uh definitions of
surprise so then all of those can be
held up and then there's a dispatch that
mediates the semantic use of the term
surprise and might calculate all 18 or
maybe seven of them only apply to
discreet so if it's continuous then
they're just not going to be calculated
or there's some other preference or you
pick a random one or you pick a
different one or you can pass it as an
argument like which surprise concepts
are we working with but all of that is
only plausible within this space where
we have the dis hyphen intermediation of
the dispatch
caller okay causal intervention
restoration we can look at the logic of
what these simulations do
okay those look all like the same kind
of plots just with different
um different interventions possibly okay
fractal active
inference D trended fractal analysis DFA
analysis H exponents looking at the
roughness of a path looking at
correlation scale-free correlation
Dimensions looking at the fractal power
Spectrum intervention Management in the
fractal
setting this looks like still mainly
in
time but maybe this is
spatial then here's free energy terms
again maybe
today this isn't
exactly the perfect representation or
calculation
but already with a self-improving
dispatch agents and operator
were wildly further than we were a few
weeks
ago okay hierarchical active inference
we could say make an obsidian file that
represents the topology of the
biofirm
simulation okay information
interventions on network
let's add like a earth plotting
component or something but it just okay
that one looked
interesting so some some
simulation some oscillatory simulation
is
happening across three
scales interaction efficacies and
strengths this one could be like a
Pokemon character
we could evaluate like farmworks
different kinds of interventions and
treatments and and
contexts these are a tractor
Landscapes we can we can dig down we
said for every single method used in the
biofirm write a mega amazingly linked
article with obsidian format okay
briefly sidebar over with the ant so it
got 25 call deep and then cursor please
ping us at high cursor. if you think we
should increase this limit I would like
to imagine the limit being
increased if you need more tool calls
please give the agent feedback and ask
it to
continue how relatable let's just run it
from the terminal
again fix this comprehensively okay so
now
while um Dr Claude is working on the and
let's continue with the
bioferm okay igen values for stability
detection on dynamical
landscapes valid
relevant
analyses
okay looks like a vector field
representation are these points accurate
they look pretty similar but maybe we
were in
a configuration set
where they went
similar okay and then this is almost at
the end of the outputs from the
biofirm wow
if we are to take a plain reading of
this we have um heat map coded
intensities blue low yellow high
then in
four semi
discretized chapters across these 120
scales through time there are these
repeating defraction patterns
like something is
happening very optical
illusion like it's just a straight line
across here but when I look at it it
looks like a sine wave
and wavelet Power Band
analyses so the kinds
of background questions that somebody
might have like how does variational
free energy come to matter in this
biofirm
implementation that's a great generative
AI Direction Venture and then there's
also all of these development the vibe
coding all these different development
directions like now please do this for
this region or please now I have this
many of this sensor and this many of
this
actuator so that's uh where the biofirm
got
I uh played around with this biofirm
specific active dispatcher so let's just
take one quick look at what the dispatch
looks
like here we can use different inference
methods so we might want to sample from
a distribution but even from the very
same distribution we might want to also
do a variational belief update depending
on what we had at hand at a moment so
again that is where this dispatch dis
intermediation comes into play where it
lets a high level understanding of
active inference like reflected by the
ontology be a applied through the strong
engineering of how the dispatch maps
from the ontological semantics on
through the implementational
pragmatics so here are these different
dispatch
calls and this is again just to keep it
local with an active inference dispatch
template but as more and more things get
made and tested and open source explored
you can imagine that in the
SRC it's possible to work out some very
generic dispatch
methods okay
so um in the last part of this stream we
will sort of half-heartedly see if we
can get this Mega ant colony simulation
going as it continues
to spiral and uh selft
talk but meanwhile
let's push GitHub update take a sip of
water and then if anybody has any
questions or ideas definitely write them
in the live chat
okay let's make a new thing
path
Network
okay okay I'll write out the prompt that
uh I eventually want to use we'll see if
the ants agents get where it needs to be
in the next uh minute while writing this
prompt uh then we'll let it finish and
then we'll dispatch this prompt to see
if we can oneshot a
thing that does something so okay see
this part of the the zero lag okay
milliseconds of lag
between applying the edits on a whole
folder and then running it again
and then instantly picking up with the
error so that's like where Vibe coding
is about the Vibes for us
humanss
but it's a different vibe for this
operator over here so okay here we are
in path
Network we want a simulation where
a
an arbitrary
ology randomly initially
generated okay here we go did we get
there with the ant 25 we hit the limit
again do we do we roll the die one more
time it's
tempting fix this
comprehensively and totally run the ant
simulation okay let's let it just one
more and then let's write out what we
want for the path Network meanwhile
though for anyone watching live write
any ideas or thoughts for what we could
do for the obsidian knowledge
element or for some kind of active
inference simulation um we we could do
anything we could front run we could
back run we could back fill front fill
any of those we want a simulation where
an arbitrary topology randomly initially
generated of
nodes reflecting
their
communicative effective
causal Mutual
influence is generated and simulated
each node is
a continuous
time active inference
agents
different nodes have can have
different relations with the same
underlying
inference methods for example different
time Deltas of
integration different levels of
tailor
series expansion
for generalized coordinate coordination
inference uh
anticipatory
inference at a big picture
level it is like there are nested sine
waves that are the level of water in the
world
all of the nodes are like ships or
towers that are doing
this real time
inference
on how much to asend
or descent in order to stay with
in tolerable limited
range of the overall sea
level which floats all
boats so we're looking for this Absolute
Total
simulation we know you can do
this we expect you to do
this all
in
iteratively
thoughtfully
oneshotting this whole
issue with initially writing a markdown
obsidian
style
schema
centerpiece and
then actually
comprehensively proceeding from there
given the
Arc of
development outlined in that very same
initial
markdown Mega
prospectus
okay ant simulation another
day new
agent
okay make it happen
thank
you
okay here we
go all right while that is on slow mode
we'll keep watching it from the side
okay so here initially as
requested it first lays out a file
structure for this package
subpackage informed package core
components okay continuous time active
inference agent Network topology
environmental Dynamics inference methods
okay
phase
one so made the requirements text file
now phase
one like it is moving quickly through
these
phases let us briefly return to the live
stream top level
okay we in this agenda did talk about
active inference we talked about free
energy principle a little bit and gave
ample cross linkings and applicable
strategies for those wanting to model
within we talked in terms of the
things about the continuous generic
model and the generic PDP there's also a
simple
PDP which is um let's just quickly look
at the output this is just for learning
the basic PDP
this
is a useful Learning Resource and it
just gives
a example of an active inference PDP
agent that you can ask questions about
and all of that it doesn't use any other
uh packages or anything else like
that
okay and there was the generic one then
there was the ant colony simulation that
our agent was still repea L hitting his
head against the wall 25 or more times
against then there's the biofirm which
was doing the active inference fractal
okay Cod this let's do a quick code Vis
with our we have one free flow so
okay okay let's
say given the fatality of the
situation what would you do
honestly comprehensively say about the
topology and
geometry of the
package okay we're going to see what
code Biz does here um we talked a lot
about the PDP and the
matrices looked at some of the
implementations for the
matrices talked a little bit about the
testing Paradigm and the runner and the
dispatch operator
Paradigm
practical these examples I guess are
places where it could be applied but
they weren't applied today visualization
methods we saw a bunch of
visuals future directions extended
functionality performance
optimization additional test cases
documentation
improvements Community engagement
contribution guidelines issue tracking
feature requests collaboration
opportunities
okay repo
information next
steps references and notes
so jump through that okay here's well
let's look at first code VI while
okay path Network looks like it's
basically done so let us
uh okay it still is generating en code
this let's see what happens
with path Network
okay
okay just running the requirements
installation
script okay looks like either it's not
going to work or it will
work and the example okay Python 3
okay comprehensively continue to fully
develop the example so that
running that one line in terminal
alone fully logs totally and outputs
safely all the
visualizations and
okay Andrew
wrote broad intentionally semi vague
question what do you think about using
your repo for generating simulating
environments you've already spoken on it
but what's next what's still
obscure good
question
so it still takes its time
um I think that it will be interesting
this not in response to the question but
just obsidian linkage the topology of
the obsidian network is only strictly
which use the obsidian linking the
double bracket
format so that's great it's also
slightly different than a hypertext link
it's slightly different than other kinds
of links that might exist so this not
the only way to link but it's cool that
um
it's so amenable to cursor's
creativity and it could be in a more
advanced setting flipped out with other
plain taex benefits or other linking
paradigms so just to say that code viz
which I am excited for the development
of I believe it offers a
contrasting
possibilities for structural and
topological invest investigation of
complex knowledge bases and I'm really
curious to see how it goes with their
development of labeled edges and some
other
features because it could give us these
kinds of systems
diagrams hopefully that would complement
different kinds of static analysis and
knowledge-based style linking amongst
componentry so two files might not be um
link to each other through obsidian but
they might be very very related from an
actual functional perspective so if
those kinds of hidden functional
relations can
be
inferred with Cod
Vis and then meanwhile we could use
plain teex
style strategies for knowledge based
linking and change among plain text
formats
it would be
wonderful okay let's see where we can
get with the path
Network see where we might get with the
environment and then see if anyone else
has funny or interesting ideas from live
chat
okay okay looks like now it uses a shell
script to run let's just look at it
first sets up a python virtual
environment installs dependencies runs
the simulation let's just see if we can
run the simulation by
itself okay
all right okay while agent is fixing the
simulation yeah generating and
simulating environments I think here we
have a lot of fun research and work I
guess uh my broad intentionally semi
vague question
is are we not just talking about the
other side of the
coin I mean single or multi-agent design
is like what we've chosen to Ladle out
from the total
scenario and if we're going to be
talking about what we've ladled out and
what we have left
unlad and we're looking at it from both
sides and perspective swapping then the
difference between environmental
modeling and agent modeling is going to
blur yet still remain in practice
totally precise
but for Alice and Bob interacting acoss
across the
interface whether a third party Observer
or one or the other asserts thems to
be the environment or the agent or they
both think they're this one or that one
or they both think the other is that or
the
other I don't think from a category
Theory SL systems engineering SL marov
blanket perspective it's going to matter
too much implementation
Al
so rhetorically or for a given audience
or
domain their entire understanding May
hinge on what the agent and what the
environment is what scale what side of
the wall and all that however that
wouldn't
necessarily break any symmetries
regarding the formulas
okay
and now we're back with the path Network
clear it run the
example okay this is a common error it
will often use like a certain
visualization backend initially that
doesn't work on my computer doesn't work
on Linux or something like that
um and then it figures out oh we're
going to use this other visualization
back end but that's
where having this Mega documentation so
it's like when I say visualize here's
what I mean by that or when I say make
it like a gif here's the here's some
good code for doing that so then instead
of
being uh Loosely associatively dipping
into the llm semantic space there's an
in context option for transfer
learning
okay let's just roll the die again and
run it
cleanly thank you for the question
Andrew Gomez thank you for joining
appreciate that xcq thank you you hello
to you as
well okay let's see what it
output
wow okay 15 agents looks like they all
converged to this
height Network topology
water level
distribution so this is the
occupancy histogram of what water of
what through the simulation
duration where it was
at so
as those watching live or rewatching can
see we started just just a couple
minutes ago with that kind of
long esoteric is
prompt and then we just had to one or
two times just say fix it and then on
the third try we're totally in the game
now
comprehensively improve this have the
have a configuration file at top level
of folder for easy
modification Ure there are many kinds
and
comprehensive approaches to
visualization
including
animations do
SK okay X Q wrote what's the game
okay environment as third
parent very
interesting okay let's look at this
config file
while path Network looks through
how it's going to implemented okay we
have number of notes connectivity
fraction weighted connectivity Dynamic
topology true or false topology update
interval then we have by interesting
analogy possibly to the micro miso macro
three- layer nested simulation from the
biofirm we have these three nested
sinewave components these are like three
hierarchical dynamical Contin ous
components and then total time
steps save intervals agent
parameters for a sine
wave tailor approximation of two might
be totally enough because basically just
following the gradient but then you
could imagine depending on the inertia
of the
agents um
maybe it can't turn fast enough and so
that's interesting like
which of the small medium and large sine
waves will depending on the delta T the
the step integration that each agent
does there's so many interesting
Dynamics again so many
that kind of the
move is these plain text generative
formats being because they
are wildly deterministically and
probabilistically
interactive
okay let's let it finish its
process yeah it's like detecting what
Linux subtype I'm using I'll never tell
you um and it that might be relevant but
again plain text GitHub
repo use it or
whatever all right so we'll delete those
outputs
okay got some ways along and then maybe
it
[Music]
um doesn't have this
package um wow though yeah a lot of fun
hopefully useful um people can go to the
doxology cognitive repo but this is just
something that took a few hours over the
last several days
so for those interested
in the
possibility for collaboration on this
through the active inference Institute
let's do that in a real repo that's not
just many many sandboxes we can copy
stuff out you can just copy all the
markdown files for obsidian and and
transfer it
over
um um we can set up that knowledge repo
and we can organize it in in different
ways so for those who are like huh maybe
this could accelerate my learning or
research with the time that you save
from that acceleration
maybe consider getting involved or
contributing because we can do a lot
together and we can drisk together in
ways we couldn't alone either so again
if this is interesting or you think like
but I just was looking for a Blog that
now I see I could just generate
locally or
semilocally if those are interesting or
feeling that you
have then
I encourage you to collaborate and get
involved with active inference Institute
and
Community because again this is just ad
hoc surfing the edge of
cursor and my own arbitrary
studies but with our own
Curiosities and expertise
pieces we can have
some information environments that have
never been seen before
so it's take taken a kind of virtual
environment
strategy I don't know if that's because
it's using some graphical visualization
method but again not to always return to
it that is where the dis intermediation
dispatch operator would come into play
is here's what packages I like to use
for this or here's how you set up a
virtual environment this way or in the
cursor rules never set up a virtual
environment always do it this way or
install package or don't install
packages but then install package could
be a page and then it could be like
here's what install packages looks like
in Julia here's what it looks like in
Python here's what it looks like in this
other language and then those kinds of
Articles can just be like you you may
search and never find
the perfect blog explaining how package
installation is similar or different in
go Julia and
python or choose your fourth one or
whatever the content might be there it
might be behind pay walls or never
created it might be tracking and cookies
it might be unhealthy in other ways it
might do all kinds of weird
stuff not that what is output from the
llm either should have the the
instantaneous Ring Of Truth
however it's trained on a lot of that
material and
so it gets us far in this plain text
setting and then if something doesn't
work we'll either know or we won't or
we'll know when we know and then we can
fix it in the plain text
format wrapper okay let's see so just
that you can only have one of these
composers but but the chat even though
it's very functionally similar we can do
that
so let's um
make one more random
thing let's just do a baseball game
here we'll use 03 mini just to use a
different
model comprehensively write a simulation
Manifesto for a baseball
game active inference
simulation this one see this one's now
it's downloading torch 766 megabytes so
that's where it's it's some Overkill is
happening so I'm going to just stop that
one but it could
happen plain text but again chat and non
clawed
models often output their text like here
which like okay that
was that would have for amazing a month
ago but we're in the point
where having it in the
composer just this is a useful contrast
so O3 mini in chat that's the control
shift L it did sort of write this
summary and action plan
for the Bas
baseball simulation
Manifesto but I think we can expect that
the agent mode claw 3.5 is going to be
doing a whole lot more
okay xzq zq zy
wrote interesting I note that the rapper
is within the hierarchical
structure
cool all
right with that I will make a last push
and then if anybody has any last
comments I'll read them from live
chat okay last
push there's the repo ending of the
Stream for
there's a lot of fun display
um methods too
or plane TX can be processed and you can
use Network ax you could use
cytoscape but the obsidian one is pretty
sweet brief little OBS
fractal for the fractal enjoyers
okay thank you Andrew yes also looking
forward to collaborate with the
knowledge graph and more xcq the play
happens in the field in which the agent
is outside
of life is a ball game
all right thank you all till the next
stream enjoy the repo get involved have
fun acting first serve leave a comment
see what happens in your own hands and
more thank you bye
[Music]